Guide to the Yale University Library Records Concerning the Construction of the Irving S. Gilmore Music Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library records concerning the construction of the Irving S. Gilmore Music Library
1973-1995
RU 270
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.5
(5 boxes)
The records consist of construction and renovation records, photographs, bid addenda, and related materials documenting the design and construction of the Irving S. Gilmore Music Library at Yale.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Separated Materials
Architectural drawings transferred to Record Unit 1, Architectural drawings and maps of Yale University buildings and grounds, Series II, boxes 659, 672-677, 688-694, 722, 726-731.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in one series: I. Construction Documents, 1995; and subsequent accessions.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of architectural drawings, sketches, photographs, floor plans, bid addenda, and related construction and renovation records documenting the design and construction of the Irving S. Gilmore Music Library at Yale.
Academic libraries -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Design and construction; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records; Photographs; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Library; Yale University. Music Library
- Construction documents, 1995; Series I
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - Sterling Memorial Library renovation, phase I
    - 30% set, Undated (Box 1)
    - 50% set, 1995 April 10 (Box 1)
    - 90% set, 1995 June 16 (Box 1)
    - 90% set, 1995 June 16 (Box 2)
    - Bid set (Box 2)
    - Bid addendum 2, 1995 July 28 (Box 2)
    - Bid addendum 3, 1995 August 11 (Box 2)
    - Bid addendum 4, 1995 September 8 (Box 2)
  - Music Library schematic addendum 1, 1995 March 1 (Box 2)
- Records concerning the planning for a new Music Library, 1973, 1988, 1994 and undated; Accession 2000-A-022 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2030
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Cardboard sketches of the proposed Music Library, 1974-1975; Accession 2000-A-025
  - Cardboard sketches of the proposed Music Library, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
- Photographic reproduction of an architectural drawing of the Gilmore Music Library, 1995; Accession 2000-A-067
  - Photographic reproduction (16x20) of an architectural drawing of the Gilmore Music Library, 1995 (Box 1)